It doesn't think, it doesn't feel, it doesn't give up.
It Follows is a horror, mystery film directed by David Robert Mitchell.
A young woman is followed by an unknown
supernatural force after a sexual encounter.
Jay Height, played by Maika Monroe.
Paul, played by Keir Gilchrist.
Greg Hannigan, played by Daniel Zovatto.
Hugh, played by Jake Weary.
Yara, played by Olivia Luccardi.
Kelly Height, played by Lili Sepe.
It Follows is a 2014 American psychological horror film
written and directed by David Robert Mitchell.
It stars Maika Monroe as a young woman who is pursued by a supernatural entity.
Keir Gilchrist, Daniel Zovatto, Jake Weary, Olivia Luccardi,
and Lili Sepe appear in supporting roles.
It Follows debuted at the 2014 Cannes Film Festival and was
later purchased by Radius-TWC for distribution.
After a successful limited release, the film had a wide
release two weeks later on March 27, 2015.
It Follows received acclaim from critics, who
praised its originality and performances.
It grossed $23.3 million worldwide against a $1.3 million budget.
It has since achieved a cult following, with many calling it a modern
horror classic and one of the best horror films of the 2010s.
In October 2023, a sequel entitled They Follow was announced to be
in development with filming due to begin in 2026.
The film explores themes of beach, chase, supernatural, friends, vision.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.